<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Škocjan Caves Regional Park</string>
    <string name="homeScreen">Find and pick up the badges on the way</string>
    <string name="zacni">Start</string>
    <string name="iskanjeLokacije">Searching location/determining position</string>
    <string name="locationSearch">Near a badge, your phone will alert you</string>
    <string name="nfcScan">Find the badge and place your phone on it</string>
    <string name="cestitamo1a">Congratulations! You picked up the first badge</string>
    <string name="cestitamo3a">Congratulations! You picked up the second badge</string>
    <string name="cestitamo4a">Congratulations! You picked up the third badge</string>
    <string name="cestitamo7a">Congratulations! You picked up the fourth badge</string>
    <string name="cestitamo10a">Congratulations! You picked up the fifth badge</string>
    <string name="cestitamo16a">Congratulations! You picked up the sixth badge</string>
    <string name="cestitamo19a">Congratulations! You picked up the seventh badge</string>
    <string name="cestitamo26a">ČESTITAMO! You successfully finished the education trial and received badge</string>
    <string name="cestitamo1b">Amateur researcher of the education trail</string>
    <string name="cestitamo3b">Forester of the education trail</string>
    <string name="cestitamo4b">Observer of animals</string>
    <string name="cestitamo7b">Researcher of the underground world</string>
    <string name="cestitamo10b">The fastest researcher</string>
    <string name="cestitamo16b">Researcher of wind</string>
    <string name="cestitamo19b">Cave explorer</string>
    <string name="cestitamo26b">Hiker of the education trail</string>
    <string name="cestitamo26c">You can pick up your badge at the information desk of Škocjan Caves Park.</string>
    <string name="naprej">Next</string>
    <string name="NFC">NFC is not turned on</string>
    <string name="status">TITLE</string>
    <string name="status2">Put away your phone. Near the next badge, your phone will alert you</string>
    <string name="tabla3b">Tick/Mark the pictures of birds living on precipitous walls</string>
    <string name="odgovori">Answer</string>
    <string name="tabla4">Tick/Mark the animals that use tree holes as their nest or for hunting</string>
    <string name="tabla3bpopup2">The common cuckoo (Cuculus canorus) lives in coniferous forests, deciduous forests, cultural landscape and wetlands</string>
    <string name="tabla3bpopup4">The European robin (Erithacus rubecula) nests among dense roots in the woods</string>
    <string name="tabla3bpopup7">The white stork (Ciconia ciconia) nests in open cultural landscape with access to rivers, wetlands and floodplains</string>
    <string name="tabla3bpopup9">The black-headed gull (Larus ridibundus) inhabits standing water bodies near human settlements</string>
    <string name="tabla3a">100 years ago, this place was less covered by trees</string>
    <string name="tabla3arazlaga">In the past, Kras was less covered by trees  because of grazing and regular mowing</string>
    <string name="tabla4popup0">The Eurasian eagle-owl (Bubo bubo) commonly uses high, dry and broken steep walls for daily resting and nesting</string>
    <string name="tabla4popup2">The common swift (Apus apus) nests in high buildings; bell towers, under roof tiles, towers</string>
    <string name="tabla4popup5">The common redshank (Tringa totanus) nests in wet meadows with low vegetation and on coastal salt marshes</string>
    <string name="gumbZnova">Try again</string>
    <string name="DA">YES</string>
    <string name="NE">NO</string>
    <string name="DrziVleci">Hold and pull</string>
    <string name="zapri">Close</string>
    <string name="tabla26">Does the figure shown in the picture belong in a pond?</string>
    <string name="tabla26popup1">The goldfish is an invasive species and presents a threat to other native species.</string>
    <string name="tabla26popup4">The red-eared slider is an invasive species that with nesting supplants the autochthonous species of turtle, the European pond turtle.</string>
    <string name="tabla26popup5">Construction material does not belong in the pond, because it destroys the habitat of many animal and plant species.</string>
    <string name="napacno">Wrong</string>
    <string name="pravilno">Correct</string>
    <string name="drzivleci">Hold and pull</string>
    <string name="tabla7">Caves are an important living environment for some plant and animal species.</string>
    <string name="tabla7razlaga">There is no light in the underground, therefore plant species cannot grow there.</string>
    <string name="tabla10">The fastest predator in the world is the cheetah.</string>
    <string name="tabla10razlaga">The fastest predator is the peregrine falcon (Falco peregrinus), that reaches 320 km/h when praying on other birds.</string>
    <string name="tabla16">The wind is caused mainly by air pressure differences.</string>
    <string name="tabla19">Is the river Reka the longest subterranean river in Slovenia?</string>
    <string name="navodila1">INSTRUCTION FOR USE</string>
    <string name="navodila2">A data connection is required to use the application. Leave the application open all the time and put the phone in your pocket and enjoy the nature.
                                When you get close to the board with interactive content, the phone will alert you by vibrating three times. A task will be waiting for you on the board.
                                Find the NFC tag and scan it using your phone. On selected signs, where a there is a badge, a question and a prize waits for you. You answer the questions
                                by dragging your finger to YES or NO, or selecting pictures that are the correct answer. Even if you answer a question incorrectly, you have a chance to get
                                the correct answer and reward – so do not give up and continue to the end of the education trail.
    </string>
    <string name="napacenOdgovor">Wrong answer!</string>
</resources>
